https://www.carlowbrewing.com/privacy-policy/

I'm looking forproductAnyAll Productsin a sizesizeAnyAll Products. Show me thecolourAnyAll Productsitems.Super SearchSuper Search××
PRIVACY POLICY
Carlow Brewing Company respects your right to privacy and takes every appropriate measure to secure the privacy of any information shared on our website.
Carlow Brewing Company is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other external websites with links from the Carlow Brewing Company website. The privacy statements of such sites should be consulted in order to understand the policies and practices under which they operate.
Carlow Brewing Company does not collect any personal information on this website without your permission and all information volunteered within emails and online forms are treated as confidential.
Information Disclosure
Carlow Brewing Company will not disclose any personal information obtained from its website to any third party unless required by law to do so.
This statement explains the Internet Privacy Policy that Carlow Brewing Company has adopted for its website.  In legal terms it shall not be construed as a contractual undertaking.
Carlow Brewing Company reserves the right to review and amend this statement at any time without notice.
Automatically Obtained Information
Some browser header information is automatically stored by the system to generate website usage statistics.
Contact Us
Should you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us or send an email to Carlow Brewing Company
O’Hara’s Brewery/Carlow Brewing Company is an independent Irish family owned brewery located in the heart of Ireland's historical malt-growing “Barrow Valley” region.
Contact Us Tel: +353 (0)59 9720509
Fax: +353 (0)59 9720496
Email: info@carlowbrewing.com
Carlow Brewing Company Ltd,
Royal Oak Road,
Bagenalstown,
Co. Carlow, Ireland.
Subscribe to our newsletter:
